

□ (+61) 403280788 | Sterryzhuo25@gmail.com | Marwww.terryyz.qithub.io | Interryzhuo | Interryzhuo

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary ₋

Current Computer Science Undergraduate at UNSW. Experience in digital Signal Processing, quantum computing and natural language processing. Research interests lie in question answering, machine Reading Comprehension and language model. Super nerd who loves Python, C++ and Linux and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Work Experience __

Monash Univeristy Melbourne, Victoria

RESEARCH ASSISTANT, SUPERVISED BY REZA HAFFARI

May. 2020 - Present

- · Working closely with PhD students in the team on several NLP projects.
- · Proposed a zero-shot question answering model that improves over the state-of-the-art QA models.
- · Co-authoring a top conference paper in COLING 2020.

UNSW Sydney Sydney, Australia

CASUAL ACADEMIC

Feb. 2020 - Present

- Teaching in ENGG1000: Introduction to Engineering Design and Innovation
- Teaching in **ELEC2134**: Circuits and Signals

Quantum Computation and Communication Technology (CQC2T), UNSW Sydney

Sydney, Australia

RESEARCH STUDENT, SUPERVISED BY ARNE LAUCHT

Nov. 2019 - Present

- · Proposed a research project of digitizing the lock-in amplifier in MATLAB.
- · Proposed the implementation structure of the digitizing lock-in amplifier in the team's quantum computing system.

Microsoft Shanghai, China

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

Dec. 2019 - Feb. 2020

- Applied Azure SQL DB/DW, Azure Data Lake Storage, Azure Data Lake Analytics, Azure Machine Learning, Stream Analytics, Azure Data Factory, or Cosmos DB to companies' data.
- Designed cloud architecture for top tier companies.
- Strongly recommended by Michael Wang

Project

Off-world Robotics Project, Vertically Integrated Project

UNSW Sydney

RESEARCHER

Feb. 2020 - Present

- · Determineing the constraints of our embedded systems, sourcing embedded boards for use on the prototype rovers, and testing them with an RTOS or scheduling architecture.
- Researching existing approaches to the SLAM problem, comparing them, and proposing a SLAM system for use on the rovers.

Py Googletrans Github

CONTRIBUTOR, COLLABORATOR

May. 2020 - Present

- · Star: 1.8k
- Fork: 371
- · Googletrans: Free and Unlimited Google translate API for Python. Translates totally free of charge.

Sphinx Markdown Builder

Github

May. 2020 - Present

CONTRIBUTOR Star: 77

- · Fork: 25
- · Sphinx builder that outputs markdown files.

Virtual FPGA Board Github

CREATOR March. 2020 - Present

• FPGA Board Visualization for XILINX ISE projects.

TERRY ZHUO · RÉSUMÉ JULY 5, 2020

Education

UNSW Sydney (University of New South Wales)

Sydney, Australia

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING (MINOR IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING)

Jul. 2018 - May. 2021(Expected)

• Weighed Average Mark 87.2, Top 2% in Faculty of Engineering

Honors & Awards

2019 Highly Commended Undergraduate, Dean's Honours List | UNSW Engineering
2017 Taste of Research Winner, Taste of Research Scholarships | UNSW Engineering

Sydney, Australia Sydney, Australia

Publication

Paper Track: Question Answering, Textual Inference, Language Understanding

Monash University

June. 2020

• Under review in COLING 2020

Service

SECOND AUTHOR

2020 Volunteer (Zoom Host), WiNLP 2020

Seattle, WA

Extracurricular Activity_

BLUESAT UNSW Sydney

POWER ENGINEER Oct. 2019 - Present

• Working on the satellite project which will be launched in 2021-2022.

• Supervising in MPPT board testing and designing.

ELSOC UNSW UNSW Sydney

ACADEMIC TUTOR, SUB-COMMITTEE MEMBER

May. 2019 - Present

• Ran crashcourses (lectures) where more than twenty students on average attended.